Kelley Student Government records, 2002-2009 C393
Indiana University Archives
Kelley Student Government records
2002-2009
Indiana University Archives
Kelley Student Government (Kelley School of Business)
C393
.4 cubic feet 1 box
The Kelley Student Government (KSG) was founded in 2001 and serves as the official representative voice of the Kelley undergraduate student body in Indiana University's Kelley School of Business. This collection consists of committee and council notes, including those related to the Undergraduate Policy Committee and Executive Board; president's notes; meeting minutes; project ideas, and other materials related to KSG.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research. Advance notice required.
Administrative History
The Kelley Student Government (KSG) was founded in 2001 and serves as the official representative voice of the Kelley undergraduate student body. KSG is also the governing body and umbrella organization of all registered student organizations within the Kelley school. KSG has two types of members: delegates from each undergraduate class and the presidents of every Kelley undergraduate organization.
The Kelley Student Government works to facilitate positive change on behalf of the undergraduate student body. In addition to implementing independent initiatives, KSG collaborates with the administration to improve the Kelley undergraduate experience. The KSG Executive Board sits on the Undergraduate Policy Committee to assist with the business of the committee and to provide the student perspective.
Arrangement
Records are organized into a single series, Administrative files, arranged by school year and then alphabetically by folder title.
Scope and Content Note
The records of Kelley Student Government span the period from 2002-2009. This collection consists primarily of KGS administrative records and is organized into a single series of Administrative files. The series is arranged chronologically and then alphabetically by folder title within each year. Materials include committee and council notes, including those related to the Undergraduate Policy Committee and Executive Board; president's notes; meeting minutes, and project ideas.
Acquisition Information
2010/045
Provenance
Transferred from Kelley Student Government to the University Archives, April 2010.
College students --Indiana --Bloomington --Societies, etc.; Student activities --Indiana --Bloomington.; College student government --Indiana --Bloomington.; Business students --Indiana --Bloomington --Societies, etc.
- Administrative files, 2002-2009
  - 2008-2009
    - Career Services Committee
    - DA/Freshman Committee
    - Exec/President's Notes
    - Facilities Committee
    - Meeting Attendees
    - Other
    - Recruiting
    - Undergraduate Policy Committee
  - 2007-2008
    - Clubs/Undergraduate Executive Council
    - Constitution
    - Electronic Files
    - Exec/President's Notes/Meeting Minutes
    - Other
    - Project Ideas
    - Recruiting
    - Undergraduate Policy Committee
  - 2004-2005
    - Induction
  - 2003-2004
    - Constitution
    - Minutes
    - Overview
  - 2002-2003
    - Constitution
    - Budget
    - Elections
    - Goals
    - Membership
    - Minutes
    - Overview